Who are you?
Where is my master,
Zhang Haiqi?
She's dead too.
Everyone but us
died.
Impossible.
Do you know how strong she is?
Why would all the people you know
be the favored ones?
Isn't Zhang Haixia dead too?
Mr. Zhang,
the Archives is long gone.
She's already dead.
What's the point of
trying to get to the bottom of it?
Leave.
No one will blame you anymore.
No one will care about you anymore either.
The people in the Archives
are to be buried
by a higher-level agent after death.
You're a low-level agent.
Strictly speaking,
low-level agents are not considered
to be from the Archives.
I'm afraid you haven't even
been in the real Archives.
You can take him away.
Bury him wherever you want.
What else can you do for him?
[Zhang Haiqi] [Zhang Haixia]
[Zhang Hailou]
[Zhang Haixia]
You can take him away.
Bury him wherever you want.
What else can you do for him?
[Zhang Haiqi] [Zhang Haixia]
Mo Yungao put Twilight Grass in Nanyang.
He then brought it back
to Xiacheng through the Nan'an.
[Urgent]
What's his next plan?
I'm sorry,
[Zhang Haixia]
Haixia.
I have to do this.
[Zhang Haiqi] [Zhang Haixia]
[Zhang Hailou]
Zhang Hailou, Zhang Hailou.
How did my student, you,
turn out to be trouble?
I'll give you another chance.
As for what fate awaits the two of you,
that depends on whether you can
overcome your true nature.
[Archives: The Nanyang Mystery]
[Episode 12]
The night tide is ebbs slow.
We didn't find anything.
Yeah.
Why is there someone there?
What...
Take a fire statement to light it.
Are they refugees?
[Assassin, Bai Zhu]
Sir.
[Lu Junxiang, Adjutant
in the Mo Warlord Faction of Beilian]
I need to know
the situation of the Nan'an.
Please
promise me one thing first.
Say it.
I want to see Bai Yu.
Sure.
Our mission to assassinate
people of the Archives in Nanyang
successfully wiped out
32 people of the Archives.
Most of them were poisoned
by Twilight Grass Poison.
But unexpectedly,
there were survivors.
They seem to have antibodies.
The Twilight Grass Poison can't kill them.
It can only make them hallucinate.
I've submitted the report.
On top of that,
the director of the Archives,
Zhang Haiqi...
appeared on the Nan'an.
She boarded the boat
as the daughter of the Ship King.
Because of her counterattack,
all the people we sent
were killed.
Only I survived.
We seldom had the chance
to get close to each other.
Zhang Haiqi has arrived in Xiacheng.
Sorry.
You finally showed up.
Sir, I want to see Bai Yu.
Take me to Bai Yu!
Let me see her!
She appeared.
She appeared!
Where is my medicine?
Get ready.
To the Dong Residence.
[A place derives glory
from its illustrious sons]
Let's go.
Who buys a coffin on tab?
On the dead person's tab
on top of that?
If you don't have money, just go.
I'll trade for it with this.
He's pulling two coffins.
Stop looking.
Zhang Hailou.
Miss Dong?
Master!
Miss Dong,
are you really my master?
I knew it...
Master.
Zhang Hailou.
Ever having you as my student
is the most humiliating thing in my life.
I should have drowned you in the sea.
So many things wouldn't have happened.
The higher-ups are right.
People like you shouldn't be kept.
Master.
I know...
you blame me for killing Shrimpie
and harming the Archives.
That's why you're mad at me.
Mentor!
Just kill me.
Kill me!
Kill you?
If I kill you,
will Zhang Haixia come back to life?
Will the people
from the Archives come back to life?
Master...
All these years,
so many things happened in the Archives—
why didn't you send me a telegram?
Zhang Haixia is higher ranked than you.
He knows everything,
yet you don't know?
You should ask him why.
Master.
I know I was wrong.
Back then in Panhua Reef,
If it weren't for me,
Shrimpie wouldn't have been disabled.
I know I was wrong.
So he knew...
But he didn't tell me
to protect me.
All these years,
how many things has he not told me
to protect me?
Why didn't I know until now?
Master.
You knew
I would kill Zhang Haixia, right?
Master,
you told me again and again
to overcome my true nature.
But I realized it too late.
It's too late...
Why did you...
Why did you let him
go to Nanyang with me?
Why did you watch him
die because of me?
You knew I am...
I am such a person.
Why did you...
Why did you bring me back
and not let me die?
Are you done?
Master, I know I was wrong.
Bodhisattva fears karma.
A man fears the consequences.
You chose to be a man
because you didn't pay a big enough price.
Now, if you want good results,
you need to start sowing karma.
Remember,
no one in this world will help you
like Zhang Haixia.
I know.
Master.
Although committing suicide
is a cheap move,
you have more conscience
than I thought.
Since you have the guts to die,
why don't you die a more valuable death?
Think with your brain.
Zhang Haixia's a smart man.
Why would he wait for someone to kill him?
What do you mean, Master?
I checked all his vitals.
He's dead.
There is a very special way
to save his life.
Only a few people in the Archives know it.
Master...
Zhang Haixia
has a possibility of survival.
Strictly speaking,
he is now
between life and death.
Whether he can survive or not
depends on whether
he can enter that place.
Follow me.
Pick up your shoes.
The serial number of the information
in the Archives has a pattern.
The smaller the number,
the more recent it happened.
[Southern Archives Document]
011.
Is it so old?
In the 25th year of Daoguang,
weird issues happened
in many villages in Xiacheng Mountain.
[Case Closure Report]
Some villagers saw
evil spirits crawling out of the crack.
The Archives were assisting
and sent someone
to go thousands of meters underground
through the crack of the mountain
to find a different realm underground—
the Underworld.
In order to protect the Underworld
to protect the people of Xiacheng,
the Archives was built upon the Underworld
to prevent things inside
from causing trouble.
But what does this have to do
with Shrimpie's death?
Keep reading.
Okay.
The agents found a body of water
while exploring the Underworld.
Strangely,
when an agent enters the water,
their body temperature will drop sharply
and die mysteriously.
Later it was found
they didn't die.
Instead, they are in
a long fake-death state
without breath or pulse.
A parasitic worm on them
can remove the toxin of Haizun.
Just like how cows and sheep
can eat poisonous wild grass—
the parasitic bacteria in their stomachs
can help detoxify the poison.
They are both
on the same and different sides.
The Archives found that
this is a good way to escape.
So I made them into two kinds of medicine.
They can be used
during the most dangerous missions—
to feign death
to fool the enemies
and bring back the secret information.
So Shrimpie's death is a fake one?
What about the antidote?
Why...
Why didn't he take the antidote?
Because the way to make the antidote
is very troublesome.
And I am still short of three rare herbs.
I'll find it. Where is it?
In the depths of the Archives.
Depth...
Depths?
Three years ago, when you caused
the trouble in Panhua Reef,
[Three years ago]
people of the Archives were hunted down.
To prevent enemy invasion,
I closed the Archives ahead of time
and dismissed everyone
in the Zhang family.
[Dragon-breaking Stone mechanism]
I then turned on
all the defense mechanisms around
to protect the Archives,
not allowing anyone to break into
the Archives.
But actually,
there is another secret entrance
to the Archives.
This entrance has a set
of complicated defense mechanisms
and changes its location constantly.
This mechanism was designed
by different high-ranking agents taking
different phases each over the years.
No one in the Archives
knows how to crack it completely,
including me.
The last agent
who participated in the design
was Zhang Haixia.
If someone can open this mechanism,
it could only be you.
So if I want to enter the Archives,
I have to break through
all the mechanisms.
In that case, Master, won't you have to—
This thing must be done by you alone.
I can tell you how to find the Archives.
But as to how to get in
and where the medicine is hidden,
it's up to you to find out.
[Horned Rhino] [Qilin's Blood] [Mud Wyrm]
How long does Shrimpie have?
[Countdown: 12 hours]
12 hours.
Down to the hour?
Haizun only appears during the blood moon.
According to my calculation,
there will be a blood moon tonight.
If you miss it,
I don't know when the next time will be
and whether Zhang Haixia
can still be saved then.
Starting now,
you have 12 hours.
Zhang Haixia's life
is in your hands.
Remember,
conquer your true nature.
This is really your last chance.
[Zhang Han] [Zhang Haijiang]
[Zhang Hairong]
[Zhang Haiqi] [Zhang Haixia]
[Zhang Hailou]
Tonight,
I will avenge all of you.
Listen.
The Archives is very large.
Go and ask around
the old address of the Archives
which now stands Haili Bank.
Go check if anything odd
has happened around the area.
Because the Archives' defense mechanism
is very special.
Maybe someone will notice something
and help you find the entrance.
You can only rely on yourself this time.
I have something important to do.
Come to think of it,
there were 18 bowls in total.
Before leaving,
the shop owner pulled Erlang's sleeve.
But the night
in Jingyang Hill was getting thicker.
Erlang, under the influence of alcohol,
with his bare hands—
Hello, everyone.
I'm the new storyteller here.
I'm new here,
so I do lack some good stories.
So I would like to ask
if there's anything interesting
that happened around here.
I dare not say anything else—
but I will make sure
you have tea and snacks to your fill.
[Talking of Antiquity and Lamenting Today]
I promise.
Just say it if
you want to listen to stories.
Who cares about the tea money?
What story would you want to hear?
I just want to listen to odd happenings
in this area.
Odd happenings?
What I talked about yesterday—
I have one.
What do they know?
Do you believe
that walls can eat people?
Really?
Tell us.
Don't talk about it. Do you want to die?
Do you know
Hongtou Mazu Temple?
[Hongtou Mazu Temple]
Hongtou Mazu Temple is a temple
of the underworld.
When we fishermen find human bones
when out fishing,
we will bring them
to the temple of the underworld.
All beings grieve for their fellow beings.
My goodness.
Look at how decayed
the wall is.
Immortal,
I will fix this place.
What book is this?
So many cracks are drawn on it.
[Hongtou Mazu Temple]
Yet, in just a few days,
Chen disappeared.
Well...
Chen died just like that.
He stuffed himself into the wall crack
and squeezed himself to death.
Some say the gaps are alive,
and some say
those gaps lead to the Netherworld.
But as to
why the wall is eating humans
and where it leads to—
no one knows.
Keep making up stories.
Yeah.
I know Chen.
He's a thief.
Every time he stole something,
he would put it in the temple.
Sir,
you mentioned that ancient text
had a few words.
Do you remember
what those words were?
It was something like...
[Southern Archives, No. 28]
something something Archives.
[Hongtou Mazu Temple]
Hurry up!
[Mo Faction Warlord Base, Xiacheng]
Come on.
Those at the back, keep up.
Okay, put it down.
Hurry up!
Come on!
Lift it up!
[Map of Xiacheng City]
Come in.
Sir, you wanted to see me?
Zhang Haiqi came back
posing as the daughter of the Ship King.
Also,
your sister Bai Zhu
died.
[Assassin, Bai Yu]
She was killed by Zhang Haiqi
carrying out the mission on the boat.
Did you bring her body back?
You don't know Zhang Haiqi.
She doesn't leave the body intact
when killing someone.
I missed you so much,
Miss Dong.
You're not Mo Yungao.
Where is Zhang Haiqi?
The armory exploded!
Sir, someone set up explosives!
Guards!
Seal off the base immediately.
You must catch Zhang Haiqi!
-Yes!
Over there! Chase!
Zhang Haiqi!
Sir,
Commander sent an emergency telegram.
Read it.
I heard that
Zhang Haiqi pretended
to be the daughter of the Ship King,
Miss Dong,
and has returned to Xiacheng.
This is due to your negligence.
We must capture Zhang Haiqi,
the location of the Archives,
and obtain related files
of the patriarch of the Zhang family.
If you fail your mission again,
you...
you shall die as an apology.
Pass my order.
Take the rest of the equipment
to the Dong Residence.
I don't believe we can't catch
Zhang Haiqi.